Hey! I'm all packed and ready to go.
嘿，我都打包好可以走了
That's right. Daddy and Uncle Joey are going on a trip today.
没错，爹地跟乔伊叔叔今天要出门去
We're going to a conference in Barbados. Right? Can you say, "Barbados"?
我们要去参加一个在巴贝多的研讨会 你会说“巴贝多”吗？
Barbados.
巴贝多
Okay. I've gotta say, it means so much to me that you guys are coming..
我觉得要你们 到那么远的地方去…
all the way over there to hear me give my speech.
听我的演讲，对我真是意义重大
And I have a surprise. I had to pull some strings..
我让要你们高兴一下 我费尽功夫…
but I was able to get everyone passes to the entire conference. That's right!
帮大家争取到整个研讨会的通行证 没错！
These babies will get you into all the paleontology lectures and seminars.
这些宝贝可以让你们自由参加所有的 古生物学演讲或是研讨会
Do you have anything that will get us out of them?
你有什么东西 是可以让我们不用参加的吗？
We're excited to hear the speech, but the rest of the time..
我们真的很兴奋要听你的演讲 但是其他的时间…
we're gonna want to do island stuff.
我们想要做一些岛上活动
David will probably want to hear a few lectures.
大卫或许会想要听几场演说
- Right, because he's a scientist. - No, no.
-没错，因为他是科学家 -不，不
He's been in Minsk for eight years. If he gets too much direct sunlight..
他在明斯克待了八年 如果他在阳光下太久…
he'll die.
他会死的
- Okay, we'd better go. - Yeah?
-好的，我们最好出发了 -是吗？
- So we'll see you guys tomorrow. - All right, let's do it.
-那我们明天见 -好的，明天见
A five-hour flight with Charlie, have a couple drinks..
跟查莉一起飞行五个小时，喝几杯酒…
get under that blanket and do what comes natural.
在毛毯下做一些自然会发生的事
It's a blanket, Joe, not a cloak of invisibility.
那是毛毯，乔伊，不是隐形大衣
The One In Barbados
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
- Wow, this place is beautiful! - Look at all these paleontologists!
-哇，这地方真漂亮！ -瞧瞧这些古生物学家！
I know. There are gonna be some pasty folks by the pool tomorrow.
我知道 明天游泳池旁一定有许多苍白的人
- My God, I can't believe you're here! - I think I've been recognized.
-我的天啊，我不敢相信你在这里！ -我想我被认出来了
- This happens all the time. - Dr. Geller? I am such a huge fan.
-这常常发生的 -盖勒博士？我真是仰慕你
That never happens.
这倒是从来没有发生过
I've been following your career for years. I can't wait for your keynote speech.
我多年以来一直很注意你的研究 我等不及要听你的演说了
- Wow! This is very flattering. - I would love your autograph.
-哇，你太过奖了 -我会很想要你的签名的
Well, sure.
喔，当然
- "Dear..?" - Sarah.
-亲爱的？ -莎拉
"Sarah. I dig you."
“莎拉，我挖（喜欢）你”
- "Dr. Ross Geller." - Oh, thank you so much.
-“罗斯盖勒博士上” -哇，真是太谢谢你了
Sure. Sarah, I'd like you to introduce you to my colleague, Professor Wheeler.
不客气，莎拉，让我帮你介绍一下 我同事，魏勒教授
- And this is Joey Tribbiani. - Are you a paleontologist?
-这位是乔伊崔比亚尼 -你是古生物学家吗？
No, God, no, no. I'm an actor.
不，天啊，不，我是演员
You probably recognize me from a little show called The Days of Our Lives.
你或许有看过我演的一出小戏叫做 《那个我们的日子》
Dude, it's just Days of Our Lives. There's no "the."
老兄，只是《我们的日子》 没有“那个”
Okay, Ross. Boy, you.. Yeah. No, no. I play Dr. Drake Ramoray.
好的，罗斯，天啊，你…是啊 不，我扮演德克罗曼瑞医生
- I'm sorry. I don't own a TV. - You don't own a TV?
-我很抱歉，我家没有电视 -你家没有电视？
What's all your furniture pointed at?
那你家的家俱是摆向哪个方向呢？
- Well, it was a pleasure to meet you all. - You too, Sarah.
-很荣幸认识你们 -我们也是，莎拉，再见
Jeez, who doesn't own a TV?
天啊，这年头谁没有电视呢？
Well, actually, I don't.
嗯，事实上，我没有
Yeah, and mine broke two months ago and I still haven't gotten a new one.
是啊，我的两个月前坏了 还没买新的
Well, didn't you two come to the right convention.
那你们两个还真是来对研讨会了
David, can you help me?
大卫，你可以帮个忙吗？
I'm trying to explain to Chandler how a plane stays in the air.
我正在跟钱德解释 飞机是怎么漂浮在空中的
Certainly. That's a combination of Bernoulli's Principle..
当然，那是波诺利原理加上…
- and Newton's third law of motion. - See?
-牛顿第三运动定律 -知道了吗？
Yeah. That's the same as, "It has something to do with wind."
是啊，那还真是跟 “跟风有关的”一样
I'm gonna go pick up a few things for the trip.
我要去为这次旅行买几样东西
I should go too. Now, tomorrow do you want to share a cab to the airport..
我也应该走了 明天你们要一起搭计程车到机场吗？
or should Mike and I meet you?
还是说我跟麦克到机场跟你们碰面呢？
Mike? Who's Mike?
麦克？谁是麦克呢？
- Mike's your ex-boyfriend. - That's right!
-麦克是你的前男友 -没错！
Oh, yeah. Wow, I had totally forgotten about him.
哇，我已经完全忘了他了
- That's a blast from the past, huh? - No, it's okay. Honest mistake.
-难忘往日情怀脱口而出吗？ -不，没关系的，无心之过
It really doesn't mean anything. I mean, you know..
那真的不代表什么 我是说，你知道的…
Monica refers to Chandler as Richard all the time.
摩妮卡也常常把钱德叫成李察
- She does? - Let's get you out of here.
-她有吗？ -我们快让你离开吧
Well, at least you took me down with you.
至少你也拖我下水了
I'm so sorry. I just.. I keep thinking about Mike.
我很抱歉，我只是… 我一直在想麦克
I'm crazy about David, and we're having so much fun together.
我非常喜欢大卫 而且我们在一起很开心
Why? Why do I miss Mike? That's just.. That's gonna go away, right?
为什么我会想念麦克？这真是… 这会消逝的，对吗？
- Well, I guess. In time. - Yeah.
-嗯，我猜是吧，总有一天 -是啊
I mean, my feelings for Richard are certainly gone.
我是说我对李察的感觉 都已经消失了
You just did it again. Chandler. Your feelings for Chandler are certainly gone.
你又来了，是钱德 你对钱德的感觉都已经消失了
Boy, Phoebe's still pretty hung up on that Mike, huh?
天啊，菲比还在想麦克吗？
I wouldn't read too much into it.
我不会想太多的
Still, a girl calls you by her ex-boyfriend's name..
但是女生把你叫成 她前男友的名字…
- that's not a good thing, right? - Let me stop you there.
-那不是什么好事，不是吗？ -让我先打断你一下
Because I think I see where this is going. I'm not very good at giving advice.
因为我想我知道这是怎么回事了 我对给人建议不太行
See, if you want advice, go to Ross or Monica. Or Joey..
如果你想知道披萨的馅料或是 为何尿尿时有灼热感之类的…
for advice about pizza toppings or a burning sensation when you pee.
建议，那就去找罗斯或是 摩妮卡或是乔伊
I'm sorry, I just wish there was something I could do, you know?
很抱歉，我只是希望能做点什么 你知道吗？
- Well, you know Phoebe.. - Seriously, we're gonna do this?
-嗯，你知道菲比… -真的，我们要这样吗？
I'm sorry, I just wish I could make her forget about Mike already.
很抱歉，我只希望我能让她忘了麦克
- Why did Phoebe and Mike break up? - Because his penis was too big.
-菲比跟麦克为什么分手呢？ -因为他的老二太大了
I'm sorry. That's the kind of thing I do.
抱歉，那才是我擅长的事
They broke up because Mike didn't want to get married.
他们分手是因为麦克不想要结婚
What if you let Phoebe know you'd be open to marriage?
如果让菲比知道 你对婚姻没有异议呢？
That's great. That's great. I'll propose to her.
太棒了，太棒了，我会跟她求婚
What?
什么？
I was probably going to do it at some point.
反正我迟早都会这么做的
- No, I didn't mean now. - Well, why not? It's brilliant.
-不，我没有说现在 -为何不呢？这实在太聪明了
"Goodbye, Mike. We'll see you at the wedding, fella.
再见，麦克，我们婚礼见，老兄
Well, we probably won't invite you to the wedding, but.."
我们可能也不会 邀请你参加婚礼，但是…
- Well, thank you, Chandler. Sincerely. - Well, you're welcome.
-衷心地谢谢你，钱德 -不用客气
Glad I could help.
很高兴能够帮得上忙
- How do you think I should propose? - I'm pretending to read here.
-你认为我该怎么求婚呢？ -我在假装阅读
I'm sorry.
抱歉
Yeah. How you doing? Hey, how are you?
你好吗？嘿，你好吗？
You said you were gonna wear a thong. Where's the thong?
你说你要穿丁字裤的，丁字裤呢？
I didn't mean a thong. I meant thongs.
我不是说丁字裤 我是说夹脚凉鞋
You really should have been more clear about that.
你应该要说清楚的
You're never gonna guess who I just saw downstairs.
你们不会相信我在楼下看到谁
Britney Spears!
小甜甜布兰妮！
Yeah. She never misses these conferences.
是啊，她从来不会错过 这些研讨会的
- No, I just saw Dr. Kenneth Schwartz! - Oh, my God!
-我刚刚看到肯尼斯史华兹博士！ -喔，我的天啊！
- I know! - Did you talk to him?
-我知道 -你有跟他说话吗？
Oh, yeah. What am I gonna say to Kenneth Schwartz?
是喔，我要跟 肯尼斯史华兹说什么呢？
You could say, "Hey, Kenny, how come you're not Britney Spears?"
你可以说“嗨，肯尼 为什么你不是小甜甜布兰妮呢？”
- You ready to go? - You're gonna go now?
-你准备好要走了吗？ -你现在就要走了吗？
- I thought we could hang out. - I can't. I have seminars all day.
-我以为我们可以在一起度过 -我不行，我整天都有研讨会
I promised Ross I'd look at his speech.
我答应罗斯我会看看他的演说稿
But maybe we could have dinner later? Out on the balcony? It'll be romantic.
但是或许我们晚点可以共进晚餐 在阳台外面，会很浪漫的
Will you wear a thong?
你可以穿丁字裤吗？
I will if you will.
你穿我就穿
You got yourself a very weird deal.
你的交换条件真是奇怪
I'm good. I have dinner plans.
我很好，我晚餐已经有安排了
- So you gonna be okay? - Yeah, yeah.
-你一个人可以吗？ -是的，可以
I got tons of stuff I could do. I'm gonna hit the beach, go swimming.
我有很多事可以做 我要去海滩，去游泳
Joe, have you looked outside?
乔伊，你有看看外面吗？
No. Why?
没有，为什么呢？
- Oh, man. - There's an indoor pool.
-天啊 -这里有室内游泳池
- You could swim there. - Yeah.
-你可以在那边游泳 -是啊
I wasn't gonna swim. I was gonna dig a hole.
我没有要游泳，我是要去挖洞的
That Mike thing was interesting. I don't know what's gonna happen..
麦克那件事真是有趣，我不知道…
- with Phoebe and David. - I do. Want a hint, huh?
-菲比跟大卫之间会发生什么事 -我知道，想要个提示吗？
I do.
我愿意
Okay, I'm sensing this is some kind of wordplay..
好的，我可以感到 这是什么文字游戏的
because you are pink with barely controlled glee.
因为你已经有点 无法控制的兴奋发红了
- David's gonna propose to Phoebe. - What? Why?
-大卫要跟菲比求婚了 -什么？为什么？
Because we were talking about ways he could beat Mike..
因为我们本来在谈 有哪些他可以赢过麦克的方式
and I told him Phoebe wanted to get married.
而我告诉他菲比想要结婚
Chandler, we have talked about this.
钱德，我们已经谈过了
You are not supposed to give people advice!
你不可以给别人建议的！
Couldn't you have made some inappropriate joke?
你不能说一些什么 不适宜的笑话就好了吗？
I did!
我说了！
A penis one!
一个老二的笑话！
Just so I know, what was so wrong about what I said?
说明一下，我说的有什么不对的呢？
They've only been going out for a few weeks.
他们才交往几个星期而已
Phoebe is completely hung up on Mike. I mean, she'll say no..
菲比还无法忘记麦克 我想她会拒绝的
David's heart will be broken, it'll be too hard for them to recover..
然后大卫的心会碎 他们会很难复合
and then Phoebe will end up alone again.
而然后菲比又会是孤单的一个人
Man, that's some bad advice.
天啊，真是糟糕的建议
Oh, hey. Thank God. You guys are here.
感谢上帝你们来了
- What's going on? - Everything is upside-down here.
-怎么了？ -这里的一切都不对劲
It rains all day long and nobody watches TV, and Ross is famous.
整天都在下雨，没有人看电视 而且罗斯还很有名气
I don't want to alarm anybody..
我不想要惊动大家…
but Monica's hair is twice as big as it was when we landed.
但是摩妮卡的头发 比下飞机时大了一倍
Okay. When I go places with high humidity..
好了，当我去高湿度地区的时候…
it gets a little extra body, okay?
头发就会比较蓬松，好吗？
That's why our honeymoon photos look like me and Diana Ross.
那就是为什么我们的蜜月照 看起来是我跟戴安娜罗丝
I'll show you guys where to check in.
我带你们去登记住房
Oh, honey? Can you make sure we get a king-size bed?
亲爱的，你可以确定我们可以拿到 超大尺寸的床吗？
Oh, David, get one for us too. Oh, and see if they have a heart-shaped one.
大卫，也帮我们确定一下 还有看看他们有没有心型的床
And with mirrors on the ceiling.
而有天花板上要有镜子
And make sure our room isn't next to theirs.
还有确定我们的房间 不要在他们的隔壁
Oh, you guys are so lucky you're here with people.
喔，你们真幸运 有人陪你们到这里
I'd love to share this with someone.
我真想跟某人分享这一切
Oh, honey, you have us. We love you.
亲爱的，你有我们，我们爱你
Okay, which one of you is gonna sleep with me?
太好了，你们谁要跟我睡？
You know, it's just such a romantic place.
这是个很浪漫的地方
I just wish I could share it with a guy.
我只希望可以跟一个男人共度
- Not Joey. - Not Joey. No.
-不是乔伊 -不是乔伊，不是
- I was just lusting after Chandler. - Yeah, right.
-我只是在垂涎钱德 -是啊，没错
So.. I'm proposing to Phoebe tonight.
我今晚要跟菲比求婚了
Tonight?
今晚？
Isn't an engagement ring supposed to have a diamond?
订婚戒指不是应该要有钻石的吗？
Oh, there it is.
喔，在这里
Yes, well, being a failed scientist doesn't pay quite as well as you might think.
是啊，一个失败的科学家 并没有你想的赚的多
That's one-seventieth of a carat.
那是七十分之一克拉
And the clarity is quite poor.
清晰度是很差
Nice.
很好
- Monica, can I talk to you for a second? - Okay.
-摩妮卡，我可以跟你谈一下吗？ -好的
David's gonna propose to Phoebe tonight.
大卫要在今晚跟菲比求婚
See what happens when you give people advice?
瞧瞧这就是你给别人建议的后果
- Well, I hope you told him not to. - That would be advice!
-我希望你有告诉他不可以 -那又会是一个建议了！
Okay, fine. I'll handle this.
好的，没关系，让我来处理
- Phoebe? - Yeah?
-菲比？ -怎样？
- I need to talk to you. - Are you leaving the Supremes?
-我需要跟你谈谈 -你要离开你的主宰了吗？
Okay, my husband just gave your boyfriend some very bad advice.
我老公刚给了你男友 一个很糟糕的建议
David's gonna propose to you tonight.
大卫今晚要跟你求婚了
Wow, really?
哇，真的吗？
That's fantastic!
这实在太棒了！
What? Are you serious? You want to marry him?
什么？你是说真的吗？你想嫁给他？
- What about Mike? - Oh, okay, you want me to marry Mike?
-那麦克呢？ -好的，你要我嫁给麦克是吗？
Let's just gag him and handcuff him..
让我们把他塞住嘴巴 用手铐铐住他
and force him down the aisle, okay?
然后逼他踏上红毯，好吗？
I can just see it. "Mike, do you take Phoebe?"
我已经可以预见到 “麦克，你愿意娶菲比吗？”
You know? It's every girl's dream.
你知道吗？真是每个女孩的梦想
Do you really think marrying someone else is the right answer?
你真的认为嫁给别人是对的？
Sure. Look, okay, bottom line? I love Mike.. David!
当然，听着，最重要的是 我爱麦克…大卫！
David! I love David.
大卫！我爱大卫！
Don't look at me that way, Roseanne Roseannadanna.
别那样看我，戴安娜罗丝
"By using CT scans and computer imaging, we can, in a very real way..
借由使用中央标准扫描法跟电脑影像 我们可以以非常真实的方式…
bring the Mesozoic Era into the 21st century."
将中生代时期带进二十一世纪
It's great.
太棒了
Yeah, you really think so?
你真的这么认为吗？
You'll be the hit of the conference.
你将成为此次研讨会的焦点
It'll be even better tomorrow..
明天还会更好
because I won't be constantly interrupted by Joey..
因为我不会一直被乔伊打断…
checking to see if they put chocolates on my pillow yet.
一直来检查我枕头上 是不是有放巧克力
- Hey, guys. - The chocolates aren't here.
-你们好 -巧克力还没送来
Damn it!
该死的！
Ross just read me his speech. It's fantastic.
罗斯刚念了他的演讲稿给我听 真是精彩
Oh, is it on the computer? Because I'd love to give it a read.
在电脑里面吗？因为我也想读读看
If you want to check your e-mail, just ask.
如果你想要查电子邮件就说吧
What? May I?
什么？我可以吗？
What's with the rain, Geller? I mean, when I signed up for dino week..
那个雨是怎么回事呢？盖勒 我是说当我报名恐龙营的时候…
nobody said anything about it being monsoon season.
没有人说过现在是雨季
- The wet season is June to December. - It's not the time, Charlie.
-雨季是六月到十二月 -现在不是时候，查莉
Oh, no. No, no! Dear God, no!
哎呀，糟糕！亲爱的上帝，不！
What, did someone outbid you for the teapot?
怎么了？有人抢先你标下茶壶吗？
Secret teapot.
秘密茶壶
Your computer. I don't know what.. Everything's gone.
你的电脑，我不知道怎么… 一切都不见了
- What do you mean? - Must be a virus.
-你是什么意思呢？ -一定是病毒
I think it erased your hard drive.
我想它把你的硬碟全杀掉了
What? Oh, my God. What did you do?
什么？我的天啊！ 你干了什么好事？
Someone I don't know sent me an e-mail and I opened it.
一个我不认识的人寄了封信给我 然后我打开了它
- Why? Why would you open it? - Well, it didn't say, "This is a virus."
-为什么？为什么你要打开？ -那上面又没有写“这是病毒”
- What did it say? - "Nude.."
-那上面写什么？ -“裸体的…”
"Pictures of Anna Kournikova."
“安娜库妮可娃的照片”
- I'm so sorry. - What am I gonna do?
-我很抱歉 -我该怎么办呢？
- My speech is gone! - It's not gone.
-我的讲稿不见了！ -没有不见
I'm sure you printed out a copy. You have a hard copy?
我相信你有列印出来，你有印出来吗？
No, I don't!
不，我没有！
Well, you must be pretty mad at yourself right now.
那你现在一定很气自己
- It's really gone? - Yep.
-真的不见了吗？ -是的
I'd like to thank you guys for coming down here..
我想要谢谢你们过来这里…
to complain about the rain and ruin my career.
抱怨这些雨 然后毁了我的事业前途
- I just feel awful. - Yeah, you should.
-我觉得糟透了 -你的确应该
Nude pictures of Anna Kournikova? She's never even won a major tournament.
安娜库妮可娃的裸照？ 她根本连什么大奖都没赢过
Well, I tried Billie Jean King, but..
我是有试过比莉珍金，但是…
You know, you and Monica have the same I'm-gonna-kill-you look.
你知道吗？你跟摩妮卡一样都有那种 我想要杀死你的表情
I can usually make it go away by kissing her.
我通常可以亲她一下 就逃过一劫
Get out.
滚出去
You know, this happens all the time to my computer at work.
我工作的电脑也常常发生这种事
- What do you do? - I usually go..
-那你怎么办呢？ -我通常会…
play Tetris on somebody else's computer.
到别人的电脑上 玩俄罗斯方块
I can't believe this is happening.
我不敢相信发生这种事
I have to give the keynote speech tomorrow.
我明天就要演讲了
I have to stand up in front of all these people. What am I gonna say?
我要站在所有人面前，我要说什么呢？
You can use a speech I memorized for auditions.
你可以用我背下来 参加试演的那段话
I don't think your monologue from Star Wars is gonna help me right now.
我不认为你在《星际大战》里的独白 可以对我有所帮助
Ross, we can solve this. I just heard your speech.
罗斯，不会有问题的 我听过你的演讲
- We can re-create it. We've got all night. - What, you really think we can do that?
-我们可以重建它，我们有一整晚 -什么？你真的认为我们办得到吗？
Oh, wait. Joey and I are supposed to have dinner.
等等，乔伊跟我应该要共进晚餐的
Don't worry about that. I mean, Ross needs you.
别担心，我知道罗斯需要你
Rachel and I will stay and help any way we can.
瑞秋跟我会留下来尽量帮忙
All right. Okay, let's do it.
好的，我们来开始吧
Well, I know we start by discussing the shortcomings of carbon dating.
我知道我们一开始 是讨论碳年代测定法的缺点
And then I move on to what is clearly the defining moment..
然后我接着解说很明显地什么是…
of the Mesozoic Era, the breakup of Pangaea. Hello?
中生代的决定时刻，原始大陆的分裂 不是吗？
And then there's the overview of the Triassic.
然后接下来是三叠纪的概观
Any chance any of this happened in a galaxy far, far away?
有可能这一切都是在 很远的银河发生的吗？
- Hello? - Okay, Mike?
-哈？ -好了，麦克？
Enough is enough. You love Phoebe, and she loves you.
闹够了，你爱菲比，而她也爱你
So get over your I-never-wanna-get-married thing..
所以不要再说什么 不想要结婚的话了
and step up!
赶快站出来！
Who is this?
你是谁？
This is Monica, Phoebe's friend.
我是摩妮卡，菲比的朋友
Sure, Monica. So good to have you back in my life.
摩妮卡，你又回到我生命中 真是太好了
Listen, Phoebe is back with David.
听着，菲比跟大卫复合了
He's gonna propose, and she's gonna say yes..
他即将要求婚，而她将会答应
but I know she really wants to be with you.
但是我知道 她真正想要的是跟你在一起
He's gonna propose?
他要求婚了？
I'm sorry, did you say something? I can't hear through all this damned hair!
很抱歉，你说什么呢？ 该死的头发遮住我听不到！
If Phoebe wants to marry David, she should.
如果菲比想要嫁给大卫，那就去吧
I'm not gonna stand in the way of that. Neither should you.
我不会从中作梗，你也不应该
You don't tell me what to do. I tell you what to do.
你不用告诉我该怎么做 我来告诉你怎么做
Just call her. She's at the Paradise Hotel in Barbados.
打电话给她，她在巴贝多的天堂饭店
And while I've got you, you've got curly hair.
对了，你也有卷发
What do you do in the humidity?
在湿气重的地方你怎么办呢？
Damn it!
该死的！
- Well, I hope you're happy. - I hope you're happy too, honey.
-嗯，我希望你很快乐 -我也希望你很快乐
Phoebe's going to say yes to David.
菲比会答应大卫的求婚
- That's what happens when you meddle. - Phoebe's gonna say yes? That's great.
-这就是你爱管闲事的结果 -菲比要答应？太棒了
No, it's not. She's still in love with Mike.
不，一点也不，她还爱着麦克
- There's no chance that will work? - No, I called.
-那不会有什么结果的吗？ -没有，我已经打过电话了
- It's not gonna happen. - Meddler! Meddler!
-不会发生的 -鸡婆！鸡婆！
If you hadn't meddled to start with..
如果你不先多管闲事…
then I wouldn't have had to go in and meddle myself.
那我就不用插手进来管事了
No matter how much we meddle, we'll never be able to unmeddle..
不管我们插手多深 我们都没有办法补救…
the thing that you meddled up in the first place!
你一开始多管闲事惹出来的祸！
This vacation sucks!
这场假期真是烂！
（欢迎古生物学家们）
I'm so bored.
我好无聊
Stupid rain. We can't do anything.
愚蠢的雨，我们什么都做不了
Well, I brought some books. We could read.
我带了些书来，我们可以阅读
Hey, it hasn't come to that yet.
嘿，还没糟糕到那个地步
Hey, hey, hey, don't mind if I do.
嘿，等一下
I'm sorry, sir, these are for the pharmaceutical convention.
对不起，先生，这些是给药学研讨会的
You feel like going to a convention?
你想要去参加研讨会吗？
- We can't. We're not pharmacists. - I know we're not..
-我们不行，我们不是药剂师 -我知道我们不是…
but Frank Madaio and Eva..
但是法兰克马迭欧跟伊娃齐罗欧…
温芭还是…
- Kate Miller. - Kate Miller it is.
-凯特米勒 -就是凯特米勒
- Okay. - Oh, good..
-好的 -喔，很好…
And that's the most sex I'm gonna have this weekend.
而这将是我这周末 仅能有的性了
Well, in that case, should I make sure it's on real good?
如果是这样 我应该确定它黏的够牢吗？
Thank you.
谢谢你
So, Kate..
那么，凯特…
how's the pharmacy game treating you?
药局这一行好玩吗？
Well, Frank, I tell you, it's rough.
嗯，法兰克，我告诉你，很难喔
I mean, is it me or is doctors' handwriting getting harder and harder to read?
我是说，是我的问题还是说医生写的字 都越来越难读了呢？
I know, I know.
我知道，我知道
I tell you.
我告诉你
But on the plus side, we get to wear those white coats..
但是好处是 我们可以穿那些白色外衣…
- and stand behind that really tall counter. - Oh, that's true.
-然后站在非常高的柜台后面 -对，是没错
You're Joey Tribbiani from Days of Our Lives.
你是《我们的日子》里的乔伊崔比亚尼
Finally, someone recognizes me. Okay.
终于有人认出我了
And it's The Days of Our Lives.
是《那是我们的日子》
- Jackie, it is him. - Yeah, Jackie, it's me. Come on over.
-贾姬，是他 -是的，贾姬，是我，过来吧
Oh, my God, this is so exciting!
天啊，这真是大惊喜！
So why are you here?
你为什么会在这里呢？
I'm doing research for a role in a new movie about pharmacists.
我正在研习一部 关于药剂师电影的新角色
Yeah, it's called Prescription for Love.
是的，片名叫《爱的处方》
- Nice. - Yeah.
-很好 -是的
This is my friend Rachel. She's in the movie too.
这是我朋友瑞秋 她也有在这电影中演出
I'm an actress.
我是女演员
So, what's the movie about?
电影内容是什么呢？
Well, I play the handsome, macho pharmacist..
我扮演英俊有男子气概的药剂师
and Rachel is my student..
而瑞秋是我的学生
who wants to learn all about..
她想要学习一切关于…
pharmacing.
-药学的知识 -对
And, see, I'm shy at first..
而且我一开始是很害羞的…
but then, I take off my glasses and become sexy, you know.
但是然后我把眼镜拿掉 然后变得很性感，知道吧
And there's some nudity, but it's very tastefully done.
然后有一些裸露戏，但是是很有格调的
My nudity in the film is not tasteful at all.
我在剧中的裸露可是一点都没有格调
So you're doing research?
所以你们是在做研究？
- Do you have any questions for us? - I sure do.
-你对我们有什么问题吗？ -我当然有
Where'd that guy get the big, pink drink?
那个人是去哪拿的 那个大杯粉红色的饮料？
Oh, and then you said that thing about bringing the Mesozoic Era..
喔，然后你开始谈将中生代世纪…
into the 21st century.
带到二十一世纪
Well, yeah. That's it?
对，就这样吗？
That's it. That's the whole speech.
这就是整份演讲稿
- Yeah. - Oh, my God. We did it.
-是的 -天啊，我们办到了
Actually, I did it, Ross. You remembered shockingly little of your own speech.
事实上是我办到了，罗斯 你对自己演讲稿的记忆真是少到惊人
Yes, but I did make a pyramid out of the bath products.
是的，但是我倒是用沐浴产品 做了个金字塔
Oh, this is amazing. Thank you. Thank you so much.
这真是惊人，谢谢，真是很谢谢你
That's a pretty necklace.
这真是漂亮的项链
Thank you.
谢谢
Hey, what do you say we celebrate? Champagne?
我们庆祝一下吧？要香槟吗？
Yeah! Save the cork, and that way, we can fill the bottle with water..
好啊，软木塞留着，这样我们就可以 把瓶子装满水…
and put it back so they don't charge you.
然后再放回去他们就不会收钱了
Oh, my God, I love you.
我的天啊，我爱你
This is such a cute picture of Emma. And is this your son..
艾犸这张照片真是可爱 而这是你儿子…
or just some kid whose picture you bring on vacation?
还是你会带在身上 某个小男孩照片呢？
That's Ben, my son from my first marriage.
那是班，我第一次婚姻所生的儿子
- Your first marriage? - Yeah.
-你第一次婚姻？ -是的
You've been married more than once?
你结过不只一次婚吗？
No.
没有
So why'd you break up?
那你为什么离婚呢？
Oh, it was..
嗯，因为…
It's complicated, you know? She was..
很复杂的，她是…
gay.
同性恋
Actually, it's not that complicated.
事实上并没有这么复杂
Oh, my God.
我的天啊
This is so cool!
这实在太酷了！
Okay. Odd thing to get excited about.
好的，为这怪事兴奋是很奇怪的事
No, it's just that I was engaged to a guy who turned out to be gay.
不是，只是我曾经跟一个男的订婚过 而他最后竟然是同志
Hey! High-five!
嘿，击掌吧！
Didn't you feel so stupid that you didn't see the signs?
你有没有觉得 没有看出端倪实在是很笨呢？
My fiance was always going on long weekends with his "tennis partner."
我未婚夫总是跟 他的“网球球友”一起度周末
My wife had a workout friend she went to the gym with every day for a year.
我老婆有年跟一个朋友 天天都到健身房健身
She didn't get any fitter.
她也没有变瘦
- Everybody's like, "I knew all along." - I know.
-每个人都说“我早就知道了” -我知道
If you knew, why didn't you tell me? I mean, call, leave a note.
如果知道，怎么不告诉我呢？ 我是说只要打电话，留个纸条什么的
"Hi. Just dropped by to say your wife's gay."
“嗨，只是过来告诉你 你老婆是同性恋”
- I know. - And then..
-我知道 -然后…
And then you try to make the best of a bad situation..
然后你试着在困境中求生存…
so you float the idea of a threesome.
所以你提出三人行的建议
I didn't do that.
我没有那样做
Me neither.
我也没有
Well, who knew? Pharmacists are fun.
谁会知道呢？药剂师们真好玩
I know. That old lady at the end was ready to take you home.
我知道，那位老太太 最后都已经准备要带你回家了
Not enough pills in the world, Rach.
这世界的药还是不够的，瑞秋
What about you, huh? You're the single one. See anybody in there you like?
那你呢？你才是单身的人 有没有看到喜欢的人呢？
Well, let's see. There was that really big guy that I was talking to..
让我想想 那个跟我说过话的大个儿…
with the really nice breasts.
有着很不错的胸部
But what about back home? Anything going on there? Anybody you like?
那在家乡呢？ 有什么吗？你有喜欢的人吗？
No.
没有
- There is. You're blushing. - No, I'm not blushing..
-有的，你脸红了 -没有，我没有脸红
and I'm sunburned.
这是晒伤的
From, you know, the rain.
因为下雨的缘故
You like someone. Tell me who.
你喜欢某人，告诉我是谁
- Tell me who it is. Come on. - No. Joey.
-告诉我是谁，说啦 -不，乔伊
Who do you like? You're not getting away that easy.
你喜欢谁呢？你别想轻易躲掉
- Who do you like? - Joey, come on!
-你喜欢谁呢？ -乔伊，别这样
It doesn't matter, you know? It's not like anything's gonna happen.
没什么大不了的，你知道吗？ 又不是说会发生什么事
What? Why not? Rach, who can you not get?
什么？为什么不呢？ 瑞秋，有谁你得不到呢？
Okay. Okay. You really want to know who it is?
好，你真想知道是谁吗？
- Yeah. Who is it? - Do you?
-是的，是谁呢？ -你真的想？
- Oh, hey. - I just left you a message.
-嗨  -我才刚留言给你
Ross and I were gonna go grab a bite..
罗斯跟我刚要去吃点东西…
but now that you're here, we could have that dinner.
但是既然你在这里 我们可以共用晚餐了
Right! Of course. Hey, did you guys finish the speech?
没错！当然 演讲稿写完了吗？
Yep! We got it. We got it. Thank you so much.
是的，完成了 我们完成了，非常谢谢
- I had a great time. - Yeah.
-我很愉快 -是啊
This isn't over, because I really want to know..
这还没完，因为我真的想知道…
Later. Later.
等一下，等一下
- So shall we? - Yeah.
-那我们走吧？ -好的
- Okay. - Good night.
-好的 -晚安
Good night.
晚安
- Okay, good night. - Good night, Ross.
-好的，晚安 -晚安，罗斯
I can't believe she's gonna say yes to David.
我不敢相信她会答应
She's clearly in love with Mike.
她很明显还是爱着麦克
You know, it's very hard to take you seriously when you look like that.
你看起来这样子 实在很难把你的话当真
Could we have a bottle of champagne, please?
我们可以点瓶香槟吗？
And I'm kind of on a budget, so if you have anything local..
我手头有点紧，所以有没有本地…
or Canadian.
或是加拿大的香槟就可以了
Phoebe, I have something I want to say.
菲比，我要说一些话
Oh, God, he's gonna do it. I cannot watch this. Let's go.
天啊，他要开口了 我看不下去，我们走
I think we have time. Have you heard him talk?
我想我们还有时间 你有听过他说话吗？
"Phoebe, I would be honored if.." Spit it out, David!
“菲比，我将会很荣幸如果…” 说快点，大卫
Phoebe.
菲比
You're an amazing woman, and the time we spent apart was unbearable.
你实在是太好了，我们分开的时候 实在无法让人忍受
Of course, the sanitation strikes in Minsk didn't help.
当然明斯克卫生设施员工的 罢工让情况更糟
Sure. Okay. Yeah.
当然，好的，是的
But, well, now that we're together again, I don't ever want to be apart.
但是现在我们又一起了 我再也不想分开了
So to that end..
所以…
- Oh, my God, Mike. - It's David, actually.
-喔，我的天啊，麦克 -事实上，我是大卫
No, Mike's here.
不，麦克在这里
Oh, hey, Mike.
嘿，麦克
Hi, David.
嗨，大卫
Chandler. Monic.. Oh!
钱德，摩妮… 哇！
It's the humidity!
是湿气！
- Hi, Phoebe. - What are you doing here?
-嗨，菲比 -你在这里做什么呢？
I have a question I need to ask you.
我有个问题必须要问你
I have a question I was kind of gonna ask her myself.
我也有个问题要问她
Yeah, I understand, but before you do, she really needs to hear this.
我了解，但是在你那样做之前 她真的需要先听我说
Okay.
好的
- Would you care for my seat as well? - Actually, yeah, that'd be great.
-你要坐我的座位吗？ -事实上会很好
Well, that's fair, you've had a long trip.
很公平，你一路这么远赶来
Phoebe, I love you.
菲比，我爱你
I've missed you so much these last few months.
我过去几个月非常思念你
I thought we were apart for a good reason..
我原以为我们分开是有好理由的
but I realized that there was no reason good enough..
但是我发现根本没有够好的理由…
to keep me from spending the rest of my life with you.
能够让我不与你共度下半辈子
Kind of steps on the toes of what I was going to say.
有点毁了我将要说的话
I'm sorry, David, but she really has to know this.
抱歉，大卫 但是她真的有需要知道这些
All right, but after this, I want to see you outside.
好的，但是之后 我要在外面跟你单挑
If it stops raining.
如果外面停止下雨的话
You're the most incredible woman I've ever met.
你是我遇过最不可思议的女人
How could I lose you? Now, I don't actually have a ring.
我怎么能够失去你呢？ 我现在并没有戒指
- I have a ring. - I wouldn't brag about that, big guy.
-我有戒指 -我不会在这时候炫耀，老兄
But, Phoebe..
但是，菲比…
will you marry me?
你愿意嫁给我吗？
No.
不
I love you, but I never needed a proposal from you.
我爱你，但是我从不需要你求婚
I just needed to know we were headed somewhere.
我只需要知道我们之间是有发展的
- That we had a future. - We can have any future you want.
-我们是有未来的 -我们可以有任何你想要的未来
Okay, well, I'm gonna take off.
好的，我要走了
David, I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
大卫，我很抱歉，我好抱歉
Just so I know, if I had asked first..?
让我知道一下，如果我先问了？
Yeah, I might have said yes, but that would've been wrong.
我有可能会答应，但是那是不对的
Please, you don't have to explain.
你不用解释，没关系
I mean, perhaps if I hadn't gone to Minsk..
我是说 如果我当初没有去明斯克…
things would have worked out for us, and I wouldn't have ruined my career.
我们之间可能就没问题了 而我也不会毁了我的事业
Or lost that toe to frostbite.
或是因冻疮而失去那只脚趾
It was a good trip.
那是趟好旅程
- Is it okay if I hug you now? - Oh, yes.
-我现在可以拥抱你吗？ -喔，可以
Because of our meddling! All right?
就是因为我们的多管闲事，好吗？
Oh, isn't this nice? It's so quiet. I could just lie here all day.
这样不是很好吗？如此安静 我可以整天都躺在这里
Oh, I know.
我知道
- Open your drapes! Open your drapes! - So glad we got adjoining rooms.
-打开窗帘！打开窗帘！ -我们的房间是相通的还真不错呢
- The sun is out! - Hey! Remember when I had corneas?
-太阳出来了！ -嘿！记得我看得到的时候吗？
Go to the pool and reserve chairs.
赶快去游泳池占位子
- I will get the magazines and the lotion. - Ladies? Ross' speech is in 45 minutes.
-我会拿杂志跟防晒乳液 -罗斯的演讲再四十五分就开始了
- No! - Damn it!
-不！ -该死的！
Walls are pretty thin, guys.
墙壁很薄的，你们这些人
"Then we have to weigh the data from recent MRI scans and DNA testing..
我们必须考量最近磁共振造影资料 与去氧核糖核酸测试资料…
which call into question information gathered from years of carbon dating."
而这些对多年来的碳年代 测定资料收集方式形成了一些疑点
Look at the woman sitting out by the pool getting tan.
瞧瞧那个坐在游泳池畔 享受日光浴的女人
She's all leathery and wrinkled. I'm so jealous!
她的皮都有皱纹了，我真是忌妒！
"Finally, factor in the profusion of new species recently discovered.
最后， 最近有许多丰富新物种的发现
Giganotosaurus.
巨兽龙
- Argentinosaurus." - Not to mention Coldsaurus.
-阿根廷龙 -更不用提冷龙
"And that's just the herbivores. I'm not even gonna discuss the carnivores.
而这些只是草食性的 我还没有要提到肉食性的
Their heads are already too big.
他们的头都已经是太大了
Which is ironic, considering their stunted cerebral development."
这是蛮讽刺的 因为他们的大脑却是发育不良的
Really?
真的吗？
"But all kidding aside, in much the same way..
但是撇开玩笑不谈，这是相同于…
that Homo ergaster is thought to be a separate species from Homo erectus.."
匠人曾被认为是直立人（音近勃起）的 另一个分支
- What? - He said "erectus."
-什么？ -他说“直立人”
- You're kidding, right? - No, he really said it.
-你在开玩笑吗？ -不，他是真的那样说
"And while there are certainly vast differences..
而当然有许多很大的差异…
between these Mesozoic fossils and the example of Homo erectus.."
介于这些中生代化石 跟此直立人例子
Erectus?
勃起？
- Homo. - Right.
-同性恋（音同人属） -没错
"In a very real way, we can bring the Mesozoic Era into the 21st century."
“已非常真实的方式，我们可以 将中生代时期带入二十一世纪”
Thank you.
谢谢
- Really great. - Oh, thanks, guys.
-真的很棒 -谢谢你们
I thought it was wonderful. Jarvis Oberblau. Cornell.
我认为很精采，我是杰维斯欧伯劳 康乃尔大学
I mean, the ideas you put forth, and from someone so young and..
你突显出来的议题 尤其是你是这样的年轻而且…
Okay, now we're just holding hands.
好的，现在我们只是在握着手
Alrighty. We're gonna hit the beach. That was really great.
好的，我们要去海滩了 演讲真的很棒
- Oh, thank you. - Yeah. Oh, and so funny.
-谢谢 -是啊，而且很有趣
- Take it easy. - All right, thanks. Thanks so much.
-放轻松点 -好的，谢谢，非常谢谢
I can't tell you how much it means that you were here.
我无法告诉你 你们在此对我意义有多大
You kidding? We wouldn't have missed it.
你在开玩笑吗？我们不可能会错过的
I'm back.
我回来了
Okay. Well, excuse me?
好的，失陪一下好吗？
- Well? - You were incredible.
-怎么样？ -你真是不可思议
You blew them away.
你完全迷住了他们了
I can't tell you how great it was to look in the crowd and see your face.
我无法告诉你在人群中 看到你的脸有多棒
I mean, did you know you were mouthing the words along with me?
我是说 你知道你嘴巴在跟着我念吗？
- I was not. - No, it's okay.
-我没有 -不，没关系
It made me feel like a rock star.
那让我觉得很像摇滚巨星
Oh, my God. I'm your groupie.
我的天啊 我跟你研究的东西是一样的
Hey, I better not find you naked in my hotel room.
我最好不要在房间里 发现你脱光光喔
Look, I took it too far.
哎呀，我又扯太远了
Hey, I thought you were going to the beach.
我以为你要去海滩
- It's raining again. - What?
-又在下雨了 -什么？
Would you look at that.
你瞧瞧吧
The only time the sun comes out the whole weekend..
这星期以来 唯一有太阳的时候…
is the one hour I'm giving my speech.
就是我在演讲的那个小时
Someone up there likes me.
那上头的某人还真喜欢我
But people down here are pissed.
但是下面的一些人都气死了
I can't believe it's raining again. It's so unfair.
我不敢相信又在下雨了，真是不公平
Well, on the bright side, now we won't have to see..
往好处想就是我们不用看到…
all these paleontologists with their shirts off.
那些古生物学家脱掉上衣
Not you guys.
不是你们
You've got it going on.
你们还不错
- What will we do today? - They have a game room downstairs.
-我们今天要做什么呢？ -他们楼下有游戏间
They have Ping-Pong and stuff.
有兵乓球还有其他的东西
Ping-Pong? Honey, they have Ping-Pong.
乒乓球？亲爱的，他们有乒乓球耶
- Let's play. - I don't think so.
-我们来玩 -我想不好
- Why not? - You know how competitive you get.
-为什么不要？ -你知道你得失心很重的
And while I say it's cute, others disagree, and I'm lying.
我以前说那样很可爱，可是 别人都不同意，而且我在说谎
- I'm not always that bad. - Oh, yeah?
-我又不是永远都那样糟糕 -是吗？
What happened when we played last time?
我们上次玩的时候发生什么事呢？
I punched you.
我揍了你
- And? - Phoebe.
-还有呢？ -还有菲比
- And? - I clunked your heads together.
-还有呢？ -我把你们的头撞在一起
- There you are. - Hey. Listen.
-你在这里 -嘿，听着
As soon as it stops raining, we have got to go snorkeling.
只要一停止下雨 我们一定要去浮潜
Some kid told me about this sea turtle. If you blow bubbles in his face..
有个小孩告诉我有海龟 如果你对着他的脸吹气泡…
he chases you.
他会追着你跑喔
I'm sorry, I can't. I'm running a discussion group all afternoon.
我很抱歉，我不能去 我整个下午都要主持一个讨论组
That's okay. I'll find someone else to do it.
没关系，我找别人去好了
I'd do it alone, but..
我是可以一个人去，但是…
I don't know what happens if the sea turtle catches you.
我不知道海龟 如果抓到我会发生什么事
You know, I feel so bad.
我觉得很糟糕
I haven't seen you this whole trip. Especially last night..
我整趟旅途都没有跟你在一起 尤其是昨晚…
Don't worry about it. It was fine. I had the best time with Rachel.
不用担心，没关系 我跟瑞秋玩的很开心
I just felt bad for you, stuck in that room working on Ross' speech.
我只是为你难过 跟罗斯关在房间里赶演讲稿
Actually, it turned out to be a lot of fun.
事实上，结果还蛮好玩的
Oh, well, at least we're both having fun, right?
那至少我们都过得很愉快，不是吗？
- Is it weird that it's not with each other? - Yeah.
-我们不在一起却很快乐，很怪吧？ -是啊
A little bit, yeah.
有一点，是啊
I think we need to talk.
我想我们需要谈谈
Yeah, I think we do.
是啊，我想我们是需要
About what?
谈什么呢？
- Come on, you guys, it'll be fun! - All right.
-别这样，会很好玩的啦！ -好啦
- I'll play if we don't keep score. - Well, then how do we know who wins?
-不计分我才要玩 -那我们怎么知道谁赢呢？
- Nobody wins. - So we're just four losers. Super.
-没有人会赢 -所以我们是四个输家，太好了
- Well, I'm not playing with her. - I'm out.
-我不要跟她玩 -我不要玩了
- I'll play you. - Okay.
-我跟你玩 -好的
- You don't know what you're doing. - She gets crazy.
-你不知道你在做什么 -她会很疯狂的
This scar? That's from Pictionary.
这个疤痕是从猜字游戏来的
I think I'll be all right.
我想我会没事的
- You want to volley a bit for serve? - Sure, if you want to.
-你想要先热身一下吗？ -当然，如果你想要的话
Oh, by the way, I'm awesome.
对了，我很厉害的
Oh, dear God, there's two of them.
亲爱的上帝，他们俩是一样的
- You ready to play? - Hell, yeah.
-你准备好要玩了吗？ -当然了
- Did you know this about him? - No idea. I thought he was soft like you.
-你有看过他这一面吗？ -没有，我以为他跟你一样软弱
- Want to make it more interesting? - How much you thinking?
-想要更好玩点吗？ -你想要多少呢？
- Ten bucks a game? - Make it 50.
-十块钱一局吗？ -加到五十块钱好了
- I'll make it 100. - One thousand..
-我加到一百块钱 -一千…
Okay!
好了！
We'll flip to see who goes first. You got a quarter?
我们掷铜板来决定谁先开球 你有铜板吗？
No. Either of you girls got a quarter?
没有，你们两个女生谁有铜板呢？
Honey, try to focus the trash talk on him.
亲爱的，把这种骂人的话 都用到他身上
- Monica, you call it. - Heads. No, tails! Heads!
-摩妮卡，你来猜 -正面，不，背面！正面！
- Tails. - Oh, what are the chances?
-背面 -机率有这样低吗？
- My point! - Oh, no, I don't think so.
-我得分！ -不，我可不这么认为
Standard rules: If at any time a player uses his nonracket-bearing hand..
根据标准法规定，若参赛者 在任何时间将没握球拍的手…
to touch the playing surface, he or she forfeits the point.
碰触到球桌表面，将不算得分
He was a lawyer.
他曾经是律师
All the East Coast is having beautiful weather.
东岸的天气十分良好
In New York, it's 72 and sunny.
在纽约是华氏七十二度 而且阳光普照
Weather bitch.
气象婊子
It's open.
门没锁
- Hi, Joe. - Hey.
-嗨，乔伊 -嘿
- What? Is everything okay? - Charlie and I broke up.
-怎么了？一切都还好吗？ -查莉跟我分手了
No. Why?
不，为什么？
Well, she said we have nothing in common.
嗯，她说我们没有任何共同点
That's crazy.
这真是胡说
No, it's not. We have nothing in common.
不，是真的，我们没有任何共同点
- Yeah, that's true. - Yeah.
-是啊，没错 -是啊
I mean, she should be with someone more like Ross.
她应该跟像是罗斯那样的人在一起
You know, I mean he uses all those big words too.
你知道的 他也会用那些很难的字眼
- Man, smart people are dull. - Well, hey!
-天啊，聪明的人真是无趣 -嗯，是啊！
Okay, Rach.
好了，瑞秋
I feel so stupid, you know? Why do I keep going after the wrong girls?
我觉得好蠢，你知道吗？为什么我一直 都喜欢不适合我的女生呢？
- What are you talking about? - Oh, come on.
-你在说什么呢？ -喔，少来了
I mean, there's you, then there's Charlie. It's like.. What the hell's my problem?
我是说，有你，然后是查莉 这就像是…我到底是哪根筋不对呢？
I just..
我只是…
Okay. Maybe you're not always going after the wrong girl.
或许你并没有都跟 不适合你的女生一起
I'm telling you, Rach, Charlie is not right for me.
我告诉你，瑞秋 查莉并不适合我
- I'm not talking about her. - Well, then, who?
-我不是在说她 -是喔，那是谁呢？
The waitress I went out with last month?
那个我上个月约过的女服务生吗？
- You know what? Forget it. - No, no, no, no.
-你知道吗？算了 -不…
- Who are you talking about? - No, I don't..
-你是在说谁呢？ -不，我不…
I actually don't know who I'm talking about, so..
事实上我并不知道 我在说什么，所以…
- Okay. - Yeah.
-好的 -嗯
Well, I'm gonna go see if I can get a room for tonight.
我要去看看有没有办法 再订到另一间房间
- And I'll see you later. - Yeah, sure. Okay.
-待会见 -是啊，好的
- You like me? - Okay.
-你喜欢我？ -好吧
- Let's not make a big thing about this. - It's a huge thing!
-我们不要过度渲染这件事 -这是一件大事！
Okay, not working with me, Joe.
你很不合作喔，乔伊
Look, here's the thing. Lately, I have been having thoughts.
听着，事情事这样的 最近，我有些想法
Musings, if you will.
应该说是冥想
- Well, for how long? - Oh, only like a month.
-多久了呢？ -大概只有一个月
- A month? - Well..
-一个月？ -嗯…
Dial it down. Listen, maybe they're crazy thoughts, but sometimes I do.
小声点，或许只是一些疯狂的想法 但是有时候我就是会想啊
I have been thinking about, you know, us.
我一直在想我们之间的可能性
- Okay, dial it up a little. - Oh, you're right. Okay.
-好的，现在音调提高一点 -你说的对，好的
- I just have a question. - Shoot.
-我只有一个问题 -该死
- What the hell are you doing? - I'm not trying to do anything.
-你倒底是在做什么？ -我试着不要做任何事
It's just, we have such a good time when we're together, you know?
只是当我们在一起时非常地快乐 你知道吗？
And I mean, aren't you just a little curious what it would be like?
你难道都没有好奇过 那会是怎样吗？
Am I curious? I mean, I'm as curious as..
我好奇过？我就跟…
George!
乔治一样好奇！
- Who? - Curious George!
-谁？ -好奇乔治阿！
You know, the monkey and the guy with the yellow hat.
那只猴子还有那个戴黄帽的男人
- Of course. I remember. - He had a paper route.
-我当然记得 -他还有个纸路线图
Yeah, he did.
是啊，没错
- See, this is what I'm talking about. - No, I know. We're great!
-这就是我说的 -我知道，我们棒透了！
But, Rach, no, this can't happen.
但是瑞秋，不，不能这样的
Can't it just happen a little bit?
不能有一点点机会吗？
- No! It can't happen at all! - Why not?
-不！一点也不行 -为什么不行？
Because, look, no one wants this to happen more than me, okay?
我最希望事情是这样了，好吗？
I have gone over this moment in my head 100 times..
我在我脑海中已经幻想过 这情节一百次了
and not once did I ever say no.
而且我从没拒绝过
I couldn't do it to Ross.
我不能这样对罗斯
- But that wasn't gonna stop you before. - I know. I know..
-但之前却不是这样 -我知道…
but I've thought about it a lot since then, and it just wouldn't be right.
但是在那之后我想了很多 这是不对的
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry too.
我也很抱歉
- Oh, God, I shouldn't have said anything. - No, no.
-天啊，我不应该说出来的 -不…
No, no, no, no. Hey, we'll be fine.
别这样，我们没事的
- Like you said, it's no big deal. - It's not a big deal.
-就像你所说的，这没有什么 -没错
- No big deal. - It's so not a big deal.
-没有什么 -真的是没有什么
- I'll see you later. All right, hey. - Okay, great.
-待会见，好 -好的，太好了
Okay..
好的…
Oh, I'm sorry, I think.. I think that may have missed the table.
真抱歉喔，我想… 我想那可能没有碰到桌面
- Oh, do you? - Yeah.
-是吗？ -是的
- Do you? - Yeah.
- Do you? - Yeah!
-是吗？ -是的！
- You really find this attractive on him? - Oh, yeah.
-你真的认为他这样很有魅力吗？ -是的
Are you telling me you're not even a little turned on by Monica right now?
你要告诉我你现在没有 被摩妮卡撩的心痒痒的？
This is the first time in our marriage that I've felt like the more attractive one.
这是婚后我第一次觉得 我是比较有魅力的那一个
All right, come on, Mike. You can beat her.
好了，加油，麦克，你可以打败她的
Knock that dog off her head.
把她打的落花流水
- Damn it! - I sleep with him!
-该死的！ -我跟他上床喔！
- Game point. - Don't get too cocky.
-关键点 -别太骄傲
Remember, I won the last one.
记住上次是我赢的
Oh, by the way, how did that feel, losing to a girl?
喔，对了 输给一个女生感觉如何呢？
You should look in the mirror before you call yourself that.
你应该先照照镜子再这样说
- No! No! No! - And that's how it's done.
-不！不！不！ -而就是这样结束了
Okey-dokey.
好了
You've each won a game, and I've lost what's felt like a year of my life.
你们都各赢了一局 而我感觉好像是失去了一年的生命
Everybody goes home a winner.
每个人都可以跟一个赢家回家
- Best of three? - That's what I'm thinking.
-三战两胜？ -我就是这样想
Should I use my invisibility to fight crime or for evil?
我应该运用我的隐形术 来打击罪犯或是恶魔？
- Serve the ball, chump. - "Serve the ball, chump."
-开球吧，木头人 -“开球吧，木头人”
Okay, better comebacks, Mike. Better comebacks.
好的，重披战袍会更好，麦克 重披战袍会更好
I got it!
我来接！
I'm fine, by the way!
我没事！
I'm just saying, I have a cabin in the Adirondacks.
我是说我在阿尔刚金有间小木屋
If you ever want to get away from the city, well, that'd be..
如果你有想要远离尘嚣 那会是…
just nifty.
很不错的
Well, I've kind of got a lot on my plate right now.
嗯，我现在事情是蛮多的
Not that I wouldn't love a weekend in the country with a strange man.
不是说我不喜欢 跟陌生男人到乡间度周末
- Jarvis? - Oh, you're back.
-杰维斯？ -喔，你回来了
- This is my wife, Nancy. - Well, get out!
-这是我老婆，南西 -少来了！
- Ross? Can I talk to you for a minute? - Yes, please.
-罗斯，我可以跟你谈谈吗？ -当然了
Is he still looking at me?
他还在看我吗？
Yes.
是的
- Still? - Yes.
-还在看吗？ -是的
And his wife's kind of looking at me.
而他老婆好像是在看我
So, what's going on?
发生什么事呢？
Well, Joey and I broke up.
嗯，乔伊跟我分手了
- Oh, my God. What happened? - Joey is a great guy..
-我的天啊，发生了什么事？ -乔伊是个好男人
but we're just.. We're so different.
但是我们就是… 我们很不一样了
I mean, like, during your speech, he kept laughing at "Homo erectus."
就像是在你演讲的时候 他一直在笑“直立人”
I knew that was him!
我就知道是他！
Anyway, I just.. I think it's for the best.
反正，我只是… 我想这样是最好的
- Hey. Hey, you okay? - I guess.
-嘿，你还好吗？ -还好
There was..
还有…
There was another reason that I thought it was time to end it with Joey.
还有另外一个原因 让我跟乔伊分手的
I started to realize that I was having feelings for someone else.
我开始发觉 我对另外一个人有感觉
Okay, Geller. Last day of the conference.
好的，盖勒，研讨会的最后一天了
You know what happens to the keynote speaker.
你知道主讲人会被怎样的
Professor Klarik, we're in the middle of a conversation here.
克雷克教授，我们正在谈话当中
- Can't you throw him in the pool later? - Or we could throw you both in now.
-不能等会再丢他进游泳池吗？ -或是把你们俩都丢进去
Okay, gentlemen, please. Aren't we a little old for this?
男士们，拜托，我们会不会太老了呢？
I mean, we're scientists, all right? We're academics..
我是说我们是科学家，好吗？ 我们都有学术素养
and most importantly, you will have to catch us first.
而且最重要的 你们必须要先捉住我们
Go! Go! Go!
跑！跑！跑！
Okay, so it's tied again, 41 to 41.
好的，又平手了，四十一比四十一
- Okay, look, enough is enough. - No.
-好的，听着，够了 -不
- I just have two more points to beat him. - Monica, that was also true an hour ago!
-我剩下两分就可以打败他了 -摩妮卡，一小时前你就这样说了！
I mean, please, look at you.
拜托，瞧瞧你自己
Your hand is blistered, you can barely stand, your hair is inexplicable!
你的手都起水泡了，你连站都站不住 你的头发真是莫名奇妙！
Phoebe, talk to Mike. Help me out.
菲比，去跟麦克说，帮忙我一下
Mike, you win this, you will get the best sex you've ever had in your whole life.
麦克，只要你赢，你将会享受到 你从未享受过的性爱
I say to fight crime.
好像是打击罪犯比较好
You didn't see us!
你没有看到我们！
Monica?
摩妮卡？
You've already proven you're just as good as he is.
你已经证明你跟他一样好了
We missed our dinner reservations, so let's just go upstairs..
我们已经错过晚餐预约 所以我们就上楼去…
order room service, take a shower and shave your head!
点客房服务，洗个澡 然后剃光你的头发！
I can't just walk away. I've put in four hours.
我不能这样走掉 我已经投入四小时了
You knew this about me when you married me.
当你娶我的时候 你就知道我是这样的
You agreed to take me in sickness and in health.
你答应无论我生病 或是健康都要照顾我的
Well, this is my sickness!
这就是我的病！
- What about the obsessive cleaning? - That's just good sense.
-那洁癖呢？ -那只是好习惯
- You okay? - No, honey, I'm okay.
-你还好吗？ -亲爱的，我还好
Shake it off. Oh, no shaking. No shaking. No shaking.
甩一甩，哎，不能甩 不能甩，不能甩
Oh, my God. I can't play.
我的天，我不能玩了
- So you forfeit? - Mike wins?
-所以你要弃权？ -麦克赢了吗？
I can't believe it. I lost.
我不敢相信，我输了
- No, you didn't. - What?
-不，你没有 -什么？
- Because I'm gonna play for you. - You can't do that.
-因为我要帮你玩 -你不能这样做
It's okay. I don't care which of them I beat.
没关系，我不在乎 到底是打败他们其中哪个
Okay, we're taking that paddle home, mister.
好的，我们要把 那个球拍带回家，先生
- Honey, you don't have to do this. - Yes, I do.
-亲爱的，你没有必要这样做 -是的，我有必要
I may not understand why you have to win so badly..
我或许无法理解 你为什么一定要赢…
but if it's important to you, it's important to me.
但是如果这对你很重要 对我就很重要
Because I love you.
因为我爱你
But you suck.
但是你很逊阿
You're welcome, sweetheart.
不客气，甜心
All right, let's get this over with. Sudden death.
好的，我们快玩吧，快点受死
- Whoever wins this point, wins. - Okay.
-赢得这一分的人就算赢了 -好的
- Oh, my God. You're good. - It's like watching porn.
-天啊，你真棒 -这就像是看色情片一样
And that's how it's done.
而这就是这样结束的
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. That was so amazing.
我的天啊… 这实在太惊人了
Well, when did you..?
嗯，你是何时…
Hold on, I almost forgot. Loser.
等等，我差点忘了，失败者
- When did you stop sucking? - I never sucked. I just didn't want you..
-你是什么时候开始不逊的？ -我从来就不逊，我只是不想让你…
- to know how good I was. - Why?
-知道我有多棒 -为什么？
- I don't know. - Well, this is so great.
-我不知道 -这真是太棒了
- Now we can enter doubles tournaments. - That's why.
-现在我们可以参加双打比赛了 -这就是为什么
- They still looking for us? - Yeah.
-他们还在找我们吗？ -是的
The bartender said they split up into two search parties.
酒保说他们分成两组搜索队伍
The herbivores and the carnivores.
草食性组跟肉食性组
You know, we, as a group, are not the coolest.
我们这一组并不是最酷的
Oh, look out.
喔，小心
- I don't think they saw us. - I don't think they did.
-我想他们没有看到我们 -没错
You know, for a bunch of researchers, they sure don't look very carefully.
身为研究家 他们并没有很认真的探索
So I started to tell you something earlier.
我刚刚要开始告诉你一些事
There was another reason that I realized it was time to end it with Joey.
还有其他的原因 让我跟乔伊分手的
I kind of realized I was starting to have feelings..
我有点惊觉到我开始对某人…
for someone else.
有一些感觉
And can I ask who?
我可以问是谁吗？
I think you know.
我想你知道是谁
I think I know too, but I've been really wrong about this stuff in the past, so..
我想我也是，但过去我对这种事的判断 都是错的，所以…
- I'm sorry, we can't. - All right. All right.
-我很抱歉，我们不能 -好的，好的
I mean, you just went out with my best friend, you know?
我是说 你才刚跟我最好的朋友交往过
I just think it would be a really, really bad idea.
我只是认为这会是个很不好的主意
Or not. I mean..
或许不会，我是说…
What?
什么？